appbistro.com 2013-05-09

# Appbistro Facebook App Directory | Facebook Timeline Apps & Business Tools

MMTG Labs, Inc. (“MMTG Labs”) knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the [www.AppBistro.com](http://www.appbistro.com/) website and domain name, or otherwise accessing any other linked pages, features, content, or services offered from time to time by MMTG Labs in connection therewith (collectively, the "Website"), you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy covers MMTG Labs’ treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that MMTG Labs gathers when you access the Website and when you use MMTG Labs’ services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that MMTG Labs does not own or control, or to individuals that MMTG Labs does not employ or manage.

What Personal Information Does MMTG Labs Collect?

The information we gather from customers enables us to personalize and improve our services. We collect the following types of information from our customers:

**Personal Information You Provide to Us:**

We may receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. The types of Personal Information collected include your full name, email address, IP address, browser information, username, password and any other information necessary for us to provide our services. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. The Personal Information you provide may be used for such purposes as responding to your requests for certain services, customizing the content you see, and communicating with you about new services.    

**Personal Information Collected Automatically:**

    * We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our Website or use our services. MMTG Labs automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested. 
    * Generally, our service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Website and its components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular show. MMTG Labs only uses this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often customers use parts of the Website or services so that we can make the Website appealing to as many customers as possible, and improve those services. As part of this use of information, we may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our customers, collectively, use our Website or services. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use the Website or services, so that they, too, may provide you with an optimal online experience. Again, MMTG Labs never discloses aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally.

**E-mail Communications:**

We often receive a confirmation when you open an email from MMTG Labs if your computer supports this type of program. MMTG Labs uses this confirmation to help us make emails more interesting and helpful. When you receive e-mail from MMTG Labs, you can opt out of receiving further e-mails by following the included instructions to unsubscribe.

**What About Cookies?**

    * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people. We use cookies to enhance visitors’ experiences, to learn more about their use of the Website and to improve the quality of our services. 
    * Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of our Website’s most attractive features.
    * Ads appearing on the Website may be delivered to users by our advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by MMTG Labs and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Will MMTG Labs Share Any of the Personal Information it Receives?

Personal Information about our customers is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information to anyone. We share your Personal Information only as described below.

_Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control_ : We anticipate that we may become affiliated with a variety of businesses and work closely with them. In certain situations, these businesses may sell items to you through the Website. In other situations, MMTG Labs may provide services jointly with affiliated businesses. You can easily recognize when an affiliated business is associated with your transaction, and we will share your Personal Information that is related to such transactions with that affiliated business.

_Agents_ : We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, MMTG Labs’ agents do not have any right to use Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information for the above purposes.

_Promotional Offers_ : We may send offers to you on behalf of other businesses. However, when we do so, we do not give the other business your name and address. If you do not wish to receive these offers, please send an email with your request to hello@appbistro.com. 

_Business Transfers_ : In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if MMTG Labs, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that MMTG Labs goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of MMTG Labs may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

_Protection of MMTG Labs and Others_ : We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of MMTG Labs, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

_With Your Consent_ : Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

CONDITIONS OF USE   

If you decide to visit the MMTG Labs websites, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law.    

THIRD PARTY WEBSITES; APPLICATIONS   

MMTG Labs services may permit you to link to other websites on the Internet, and other websites may contain links to the Websites. These other websites are not under MMTG Labs control, and such links do not constitute an endorsement by MMTG Labs of those other websites or the services offered through them. The privacy and security practices of websites linked to or from the MMTG Labs websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy, and MMTG Labs is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites.    

**SPECIFICALLY, the Website will link to Facebook webpages and provide links to various Facebook applications. MMTG LABS HAS NO CONTROL OVER FACEBOOK’S PRIVACY PRACTICES** **OR THE PRIVACY PRACTICES OF THE OWNERS OR OPERATORS OF ANY OF THE APPLICATIONS.**   

Is Personal Information About me Secure?

Your MMTG Labs account Personal Information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to ensure that there is no unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

MMTG Labs endeavors to protect user information to ensure that user account information is kept private, however, MMTG Labs cannot guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. 

what personal information can i access?

MMTG Labs allows you to access certain personal information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information. Please see your account settings for more information.    

What Choices Do I Have?

You may request deletion of your MMTG Labs account by sending an e-mail to hello@appbistro.com. Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account. 

If you do not wish to receive email or other mail from us, please indicate this preference during the registration process. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Website, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

MMTG Labs may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Website or sending you an email. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Website after such changes have been first posted.

Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy on our Website, please send us a detailed message at hello@appbistro.com. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

Effective Date: May 1, 2010

Email: hello@appbistro.com

Phone: (415) 413-8227

Address: 311 Oak St #842, Oakland, CA, 94607
